Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art rental records, 1961-1973 COR0003.1.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Consignments, 1962-1973; Series 1
  - Individual artists, 1962-1973; Series 1 Subseries 4
    - Hall, Everson, 1970 July 07-1971 December 07; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 85)
    - Halsted, Joy, 1969 November 14; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 86)
    - Hedin, Arvin, 1969 December 21, 1970 May 02; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 87)
    - Heltzel, Charles C., 1969 April 17-1970 May 23; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 88)
    - Hensley, Jackson, 1965 January 18-1972 August 08; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 89)
    - Herdeck, Constance, 1970 September 17-1972 September 21; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 90)
    - Hill, Marvin, 1971 February 09-1972 March 17; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 91)
    - Hoare, Sr. Gabriel Mary, 1972 March 19-1973 May 10; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 92)
    - Hoffmaster, Paul, 1970 September 18-1973 February 20; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 93)
    - Holland, Susan, 1969 November 19-1973 March 14; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 94)
    - Hompson, Davi Det, 1970 June 10; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 95)
    - Hoover, Nan, 1962 February 24; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 96)
    - Horning, Robert, 1970 September 18, 1970 December 04; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 97)
    - Hudson, Andrew, 1969 August 28-1971 December 07; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 98)
    - Huff, Robert, 1974 June 28, 1974 July 01; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 99)
    - Hughes, Cassandra, 1969 October 09-1972 April 13; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 100)
    - Hull, Sigrid, 1969 March 08-1971 December 10; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 101)
    - Hynes, Hilary, 1969 November 20, 1970 March 25; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 102)
    - Isham, Sheila, 1969 December 03-1973 May 10; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 103)
    - Johnson, Jocko, 1973 February 23- 1973 August 17; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 104)
    - Johnson, Robert, 1970 September 18-1974 July 09; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 105)
    - Jones, Allan, 1965 February 2801965 November 08; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 106)
    - Jones, Lou, 1970 October 29-1972 February 02; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 107)
    - Jonspottir, Ragnheidur, 1962 October 16-1970 August 29; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 107)
    - Joseph, Helen, 1966 January 06-1966 September 19; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 108)
    - Joseph, Joel, 1972 February 01-1972 February 02; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 109)
    - Kainen, Jacob, 1965 February 17-1972 February 23; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 110)
    - Kallweit, Jalal, 1970 November 20-1973 March 09; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 110)
    - Kappraff, Susan, 1970 January 15-1970 July 10; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 111)
    - Kardos, Jan, 1971 February 01-1972 February 02; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 112)
    - Karelitz, Judy, 1971 February 20-1972 February 04; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 113)
    - Kendall, Margarida, 1972 October 05, 1973 February 15; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 114)
    - Kennedy, Paul, 1972 October 31, 1973 February 15; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 115)
    - Kerne, Barbara, 1969 December 04-1973 February 22; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 116)
    - Kirch, Ingrid, 1972 February 02, 1973 February 04; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 117)
    - Kirsh, Joseph, 1972 February 02, 1972 September 07; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 118)
    - Klaidman, Kitty, 1970 June 09-1973 March 14; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 119)
    - Knight, Jenny Lee, 1970 September 30-1973 March 06; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 120)
    - Knight, Nat, 1969 September 03, 1969 October 08; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 121)
    - Knuerr, Allan, 1972 September 11; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 122)
    - Kofler, John G., 1972 January 26-1972 February 04; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 123)
    - Konopisos, D.A., 1971 July 14-1973 February 26; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 124)
    - Kramer, Cecelia, 1971 January 15; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 125)
    - Kramer, Rueben, 1962 October 30, 1962 November 06; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 126)
    - Lahey, Carlotta and Richard, 1965 March 03-1966 March 15; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 127)
    - Laliberte, Norman, 1971 June 05-1971 December 09; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 128)
    - Lane, William, 1969 October 11-1972 March 18; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 129)
    - LeClaire, Isabella, 1972 February 02-1972 December 27; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 130)
    - Leight, Fran, 1970 April 25-1972 March 22; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 131)
    - Liao, Shiou-Ping, 1970 November 25; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 132)
    - Liberman, Alexander, 1974 July 01; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 133)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1972 March 14; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 134)
    - Locke, Earl, 1972 March 04-1972 October 25; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 135)
    - Locker, Tom, 1964 February 01-1964 February 17; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 136)
    - Lombardo, Bill, 1973 February 06; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 137)
    - Longo, Vincent, 1974 June 24, 1978 November 21; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 138)
    - Lorens, Emalie, 1971 November 03-1972 August 21; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 139)
    - Love, Jane, 1969 September 17-1972 February 02; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 140)
    - Ludlum, Stephen J., 1970 June 16-1971 December 06; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 141)
    - MacDonald, Kevin, 1972 October 03, 1973 February 20; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 142)
    - Mackey, 1970 January 11-1971 December 17; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 143)
    - Maffei, Norman, 1972 January 31-1973 July 17; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 144)
    - Mago, Rafael Bogarin, 1969 January 02-1971 May 26; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 145)
    - Maldanado, Estuardo, 1970 October 28-1978 November 20; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 146)
    - Malt, Harold Lewis, 1971 October 26; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 147)
    - Maltz, Elva, 1971 April 23-1972 April 20; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 148)
    - Marek, Krystyna, 1970 October 1-1973 March 05; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 149)
    - Mason, Philip, 1970 September 18-1971 July 26; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 150)
    - Maurer, Leonard, April 17; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 151)
    - McAdams, Alfred, 1965 November 12-1966 January 04; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 152)
    - McDonald, Kevin, 1970 September 18; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 153)
    - McKay, Martha, 1968 November 01-1973 March 14; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 154)
    - Mead, Christine, 1972 March 28-1972 November 30; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 155)
    - Meixner, Ruth, 1969 November 05, 1969 November 14; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 156)
    - Middleman, Susan, 1969 November 01-1970 May 06; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 157)
    - Miller, Rosilind, 1970 October 13-1972 March 03; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 158)
    - Minujin, Marta, 1972 March 27- 1973 May 03; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 159)
    - Miotte, Jean, 1973 April 02; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 160)
    - Monson, James Paul, 1971 April 23-1973 November 12; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 161)
    - Morelli, Paulette, 1969 December 06, 1969 December 23; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 162)
    - Morris, Robert, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 163)
    - Morrison, Ralph, 1968 November 11-1973 March 21; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 164)
    - Morrow, Boyd, 1970 October 22-1973 March 30; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 165)
    - Morse, Breton, 1971 June 29-1978 December 19; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 166)
    - Mosquera, Christopher, 1973 February; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 167)
    - Mugumu, 1970 February 17; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 168)
    - Murphy, Patricia, 1970 October 16-1971 December 8; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 169)
    - Namias, Edith, 1964 March 10-1973 March 15; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 170)
    - Needham, Mazalyn, 1963 November 1; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 171)
    - Nelson, Karen L., 1972; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 172)
    - Newman, Bill, 1972 February 2-1973 February 23; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 173)
    - Newmann, Bob, 1969 November 14-1970 October 5; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 174)
    - Lowell, Nesbitt, 1963 April 6; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 175)
    - Nicholson, Robert, 1972 February 2-1973 February 23; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 176)
    - Niizuma, Minoru, 1970 March 12-1971 July 26; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 177)
    - Nillson, Gladys, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 178)
    - Nutt, Jim, 1970 September 22-1973 March 16; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 179)
    - On, George, 1969 October 8-1973 February 22; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 180)
    - Paris, Lena, 1970 March 19, 1973 February 23; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 181)
    - Parmalee, Terry, 1972 September 14-1973 March 8; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 182)
    - Patterson, Chalres, 1966 May 6-1972 July 28; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 183)
    - Peiperl, Adam, 1971 April 5-1971 April 16; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 184)
    - Perfetti, Tom, 1971 February 26-1974 November 7; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 185)
    - Perlmutter, Jack, 1965 March 16-1974 July 16; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 186)
    - Peterson, Fred, 1970 November 27-1973 April 24; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 187)
    - Piano, R.C., 1971 October 19-1972 March 20; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 188)
    - Pierce, Michael, 1972 October 24-1973 April 30; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 189)
    - Pileage, Josef, 1963 October 22; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 190)
    - Pitts, Fred, 1971 September 16-1973 March 2; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 191)
    - Poleskie, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 192)
    - Pond, Clayton, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 193)
    - Porta, Guilio, 1972 January 2-1973 June 15; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 194)
    - Rambisson, Sonnylal, 1969 September 15-1978 November 17; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 195)
    - Rankine, V.V., 1968 March 18-1971 June 29; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 196)
    - Reed, Paul, 1969 February 4-1973 February 23; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 197)
    - Reichard, Stephen B, 1970 July 9-1973 March 17; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 198)
    - Retallack, Joan, 1971 August 12-1973 February 13; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 199)
    - Reuben, Isadore, 1970 September 19; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 200)
    - Richardson, William, 1970 December 8-1972 January 8; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 201)
    - Rocca, Sue Ellen, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 202)
    - Rodriguez, Paul, 1972 February 25; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 203)
    - Rothman, Harry E., 1971 September 30-1973 February 20; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 204)
    - Rothschild, Amalie, 1962 September 26-1972 May 16; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 205)
    - Rowe, Dolly, 1971 April 20-1972 June 13; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 206)
    - Rubadoux, Craig, 1974 June 28; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 207)
    - Ruben, Margit, 1970 April 15-1973 February 27; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 208)
    - Russo, Alex, 1964 November 12-1973 May 25; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 209)
    - Rutherford, Eric A., 1970 November 12-1979 January 26; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 210)
    - Sanchez, Edgar, 1971 November 10-1978 November 22; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 211)
    - SanJuan, Pedro, 1965 December 06-1966 February 07; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 1)
    - Sauber, Gladys, 1972 February 01, 1972 February 06; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 2)
    - Semon, Michon, 1970 September 19-1973 March 12; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 3)
    - Shafer, Mike, 1969 November 14-1972 October 03; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 4)
    - Shafer, Stan, 1971 April 16-1973 March 09; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 5)
    - Shapiro, MS, 1970 October 09; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 6)
    - Sheaks, Barclay, 1969 April 08-1972 September 07; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 7)
    - Sheldon, George, 1966 March 23-1973 March; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 8)
    - Shenker, Eric, 1972 December 21-1972 December 28; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 9)
    - Sherman, Elizabeth May, 1970 March 09-1978 November 21; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 10)
    - Shields, Anne Kesler, 1972 February 19, 1973 March 02; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 11)
    - Shinohara, Ushio, 1970 January 20, 1973 February 20; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 12)
    - Shniderman, Mrs. Craig, 1970 November 03-1971 March 23; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 13)
    - Sibley, Charles K., 1966 April 18, 1966 April 22; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 14)
    - Sibulkin. Judith, 1965 November 16; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 15)
    - Silver, Jody, 1970 March 13-1973 March 11; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 16)
    - Singh, Livleen, 1970 September 18; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 17)
    - Singletary, Robert, 1970 October 01-1971 March 04; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 18)
    - Snyder, Earl, 1970 March 18-1978 November 17; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 19)
    - Sockwell, Carroll, 1970 October 28-1972 October 12; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 20)
    - Solotaire, Robert, 1965 February 20-1970 June 13; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 21)
    - Sperber, Phyllis, 1970 March 18; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 22)
    - Stark, Bob, 1970 September 18-1972 December 22; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 23)
    - Stark, Ron, 1973 June 5; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 24)
    - Staton, David, 1970 October 16-1971 December 02; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 25)
    - Stephens, David, 1971 March 26; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 26)
    - Stern, Wendy, 1970 September 17; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 27)
    - Steward, Richard, 1972 May 18-1973 February 27; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 28)
    - Steyaert, Elsa, 1963 April 11; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 29)
    - Stocker, Helen, 1971 September 09, 1971 September 19; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 30)
    - Stohlhuth, Harold, 1969 September 18-1971 October 23; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 31)
    - Stovall, Lou, 1970 September 16-1973 February 27; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 32)
    - Stroy, Dennis Jr., 1969 October 21-1970 January 02; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 33)
    - Summers, Carol, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 34)
    - Takai, 1968 June 03-1969 May 03; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 35)
    - Thelin, Valfred, 1970 December 01; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 36)
    - Thomas, Alma, 1973 February 15; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 37)
    - Thomas, James L., 1970 November 18-1972 February 03; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 38)
    - Thomas, Peter G., 1961 December 28-1962 January 28; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 39)
    - Thrift, Walter, 1967 October 31-1972 October 19; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 40)
    - Trova, Ernest, 1969; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 41)
    - Twitty, James, 1963 August 09-1973 May 21; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 42)
    - Urquhart, Eva Marie, 1972 October 06, 1973 February 22; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 43)
    - Van Landingham, Marian, 1971 June 17-1973 February 08; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 44)
    - Viert, Haler, 1973 April 03; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 45)
    - Vishniac, Roman, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 46)
    - Walters, Candy, 1971 May 28, 1971 December 09; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 47)
    - Washburn, Charles, 1970 September 18-1973 September 10; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 48)
    - Weeks, Arthur, 1965 November 10-1978 November 21; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 49)
    - White, Franklin, 1972 January 13-1973 May 01; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 50)
    - White, Joe, 1972 May 15-1973 March 20; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 51)
    - White, Patricia, 1970 September 25-1974 July 01; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 52)
    - Williams, Rhoda, 1970 October 17-1973 March 08; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 53)
    - Williams, Ruth S., 1969 October 25-1973 February 20; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 54)
    - Willis, Robert, 1968 March 18-1972 February 01; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 55)
    - Winer, Elizabeth, 1971 July 04, 1971 December 09; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 56)
    - Woehrman, Ralph, 1974 June 24-1979 January 26; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 57)
    - Wolfe, Tom, 1972 September 26; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 58)
    - Wong, Frederick, 1968 June 13-1973 February 27; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 59)
    - Wood, Anne, 1970 September 22, 1971 February 05; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 60)
    - Wright, Frank, 1968 November 08; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 61)
    - Yong, Po, 1970 March 19-1972 March 22; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 62)
    - Young, Kenneth, 1968 October 18-1973 April 28; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 63)
  - Summary report on Art Rental, 1962-1965; Series 1 Subseries 5
    This subseries file contains lists of galleries, artists, titles of art work, and the number of times art works were rented, with a notation on whether the works were sold or returned to the galleries and artists. These lists were maintained from 1962-1965, and are handwritten on yellow legal paper.
    - Summary Report on Art Rental, 1962-1965; Series 1, Subseries 5 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 64)
- Administration, 1961-1981; Series 2
  Organized into 14 subseries: New York art rental trips; Administration information and operating ideas; Correspondence; Inventory and shipping lists; Operating reports and procedures; Rental procedures--corporate and individual; Finanacial reports; Balance sheets and Art rental accounts; Bills due: 1962-1967; Maintenance, repairs, framing; Publicity and public relations; Legal problems/suits; Insurance; and Sample forms.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Subseries 12, Legal problems and suits, may contain materials with restricted content. All requests to use materials in Subseries 12 must be reviewed and approved by the Public Services Librarian.
  All other subseries are open for research.
  - New York art rental trips, 1961-1963, 1965-1966; Series 2 Subseries 1
    This subseries contains correspondence with gallery directors arranging for appointments; itineraries and appointment schedules for the various New York galleries; handwritten and typewritten notes listing artist, art work and price, selected from each gallery; itemized expense accounts for trips; and related miscellaneous memos.
    - NY Rental Trip, 1963 (September), Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 65)
    - NY Rental Trip, 1965 (September), Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 66)
    - NY Rental Trip, 1966 (September), Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 67)
    - NY Rental Trip, 1967 (September), Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 68)
  - Administration information and operating ideas, 1972, prior to 1972, 1969; Series 2 Subseries 2
    This subseries contains general information and ideas about and for the ARG. There are such items as a drawing for a proposed gallery arrangement; a procedure and information sheet for consignments from individual artists; suggestions for volunteers; the ARG rental policy; definitions of artistic processes and terms; ideas for shows; brochures from other art rental/sales galleries; guidelines for operations and renovations; recommendations for improving and strengthening the ARG; and a statement of purpose.
    - Art Rental Gallery 1969-Administrative Information and Operating Ideas, Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 69)
    - Art Rental Gallery-Prior to 1972-Administrative Information and Operating Ideas, Pre-1972; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 70)
    - Art Rental Gallery 1972-Administrative Information and Operating Ideas, Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 71)
  - Correspondence, 1958-1981; Series 2 Subseries 3
    This subseries is arranged chronologically by year.
    This subseries contains memos and in-house correspondence; legal correspondence; communications between the ARG, their renters and potential buyers; and correspondence with shipping companies.
    - Art Rental Gallery Correspondence, 1958-1962; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 72)
    - Art Rental Gallery Correspondence, 1962; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 73)
    - Art Rental Gallery Correspondence, 1963; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.003, Folder 74)